This is all your fault.
这都是你的错
-How's it my fault? You left your book in the limo. -It's your fault I was even in a limo.
-怎么就是我的错了   -你把你的本子忘在轿车里的 就是你的错我才坐上了轿车
I can't even function without my day planner.
没了记事本我都没法正常生活
You know, I'm... I'm trying to think of a reason to keep on living.Still trying.
我正努力想个能继续活下去的理由呢 还在努力
Still trying. Still trying.
继续努力   仍然在努力
-You need to chill, okay? You just need to relax.-Relax?
-你需要冷静一下   好吧   你只需要放松心情 -放松心情
How am I supposed to relax? My relaxation tapes are in my day planner.
你要我怎么放松 只有日程计划本才能使我放松
Snap out of it!
冷静一下
Don't hit me!
别打我
Listen, okay, your speech doesn't start until 3 o'clock. That gives you...
听着   你的演讲3点才开始   你还有
Three and a half hours!
3个半小时呢
Four and a half.
4个半小时
Same thing.
都一样
Roxy,
罗克茜
spontaneity doesn't just happen. Okay?
不是说演讲就能演讲  知道吗
You've to get there and rehearse.
你得先赶到那儿排练
Besides, where am I gonna get cleaned up?
还有   我要到哪儿梳洗干净
I have a plan.
我有个主意